<resources>
    <string name="app_name">4k Wallpaper</string>
    <string name="nav_open">open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">close</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">Privacy Policy for  4K Wallpaper App\n\nEffective Date: 01/12/2023\n\nThank you for choosing 4K Wallpaper App! This Privacy Policy outlines how we collect, use, and safeguard your personal information when you use our application.\n\n1. Information We Collect\n1.1 Personal Information\nUser-Provided Information: When you create an account or interact with the app, we may collect personal information such as your name, email address, and profile picture.\n1.2 Non-Personal Information\nUsage Data: We collect non-personal information about how you use the app, including your device type, operating system, and app usage statistics.\n\nWallpaper Preferences: The app may store information about your wallpaper preferences to enhance your user experience.\n\n2. How We Use Your Information\nWe use the collected information for the following purposes:\n\nPersonalization: To provide personalized content, including wallpapers based on your preferences.\n\nCommunication: To send you important updates, notifications, and promotional materials.\n\nImprovement: To analyze app usage and enhance its features and functionality.\n\n3. Data Security\nWe prioritize the security of your information. We implement industry-standard measures to protect your personal data from unauthorized access, disclosure, or alteration.\n\n4. Third-Party Services\nOur app may integrate with third-party services for analytics, advertising, or other purposes. Please review the privacy policies of these services as we do not control their practices.\n\n5. User Control and Opt-Out\nYou have the right to:\n\nAccess and Update: Review and update your personal information within the app settings.\n\nOpt-Out: You can opt-out of promotional communications by following the instructions included in each email or contacting us directly.\n\n6. Children\'s Privacy\nOur app is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If you believe that we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us to delete it.\n\n7. Changes to this Privacy Policy\nWe may update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our practices. Check the app for the latest version.\n\n8. Contact Us\nIf you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at arqam.appdev@gmail.com.\n\nBy using  4K Wallpaper App, you agree to the terms outlined in this Privacy Policy.\n\n</string>
    <string name="about_us">Welcome to 4k Wallpaper, the ultimate destination for stunning 4K wallpapers that transform your device into a visual masterpiece. Our passion for art and technology drives us to curate a diverse collection of high-resolution wallpapers, providing you with an immersive and personalized experience.\n\nOur Mission\nAt 4k Wallpaper, we believe in the power of aesthetics to enhance your digital world. Our mission is to elevate your device\'s display by offering a handpicked selection of breathtaking 4K wallpapers. We strive to bring beauty, inspiration, and creativity to your fingertips, allowing you to customize your device in a way that reflects your unique style.\n\nWhat Sets Us Apart\nCurated Selection: Our team of passionate curators selects each wallpaper meticulously, ensuring a diverse and high-quality collection that caters to various tastes and preferences.\n\nHigh-Resolution Brilliance: Immerse yourself in the brilliance of 4K resolution. Every wallpaper is optimized to make your screen come alive with vibrant colors and exquisite details.\n\nUser-Friendly Interface: We\'ve designed our app with you in mind. Navigate seamlessly through our extensive library, find the perfect wallpaper, and set it as your background with just a few taps.\n\nConnect with Us\nWe value your experience and welcome your feedback. Connect with us on social media to stay updated on the latest additions, get behind-the-scenes insights, and share your favorite wallpapers with the community.Contact Us: arqam.appdev@gmail.com\nThank You\nThank you for choosing 4K Wallpapers to elevate your device\'s visual appeal. We\'re committed to providing you with an unparalleled wallpaper experience, and we look forward to being a part of your digital journey.\n\n4k Wallpapers Team</string>

</resources>